WHEN YOU FEEL
INVISIBLE AND ALONE,...
LIKE NO ONE
TRULY SEES YOUR
HEART.
THE BIBLE SAYS,...
THE LORD IS
CLOSE TO THE
BROKEN HEARTED AND
SAVES THOSE WHO
ARE CRUSHED
IN SPIRIT.
PSALM 34 -18.
IMAGINE SITTING QUIETLY
IN YOUR ROOM,...
THE SILENCE WRAPPING
AROUND YOU LIKE
A HEAVY BLANKET.
YOU REACH OUT,...
BUT NO ONE
ANSWERS.
YET,...
RIGHT THERE,...
GOD'S PRESENCE IS
NEAR,...
QUIETLY COMFORTING EVERY
ACHE AND WHISPERING
PEACE
TO YOUR SOUL.
EVEN IN MOMENTS
WHEN LONELINESS FEELS
OVERWHELMING,...
HIS PROMISE REMINDS
US YOU ARE
NEVER TRULY ALONE.
HIS LOVE IS
A CONSTANT TENDER
EMBRACE.
SO,...
WHEN THE WORLD...
IF YOU REALLY
BELIEVE IN GOD'S
MERCY,...
LISTEN CAREFULLY.
TOMORROW,...
A LIFE -CHANGING
PRAYER IS BEING
SHARED,
BUT IF YOU'RE
NOT FOLLOWING GOD'S
MESSAGES,...
YOU'LL MISS IT.
THIS MIGHT BE
THE REMINDER YOUR
HEART HAS BEEN
CRYING OUT FOR.
FOLLOW NOW,...
SO YOU DON'T
MISS WHAT GOD
HAS PLANNED FOR
YOU.